# **Andrey Yastrebov**

iOS Software Engineer Born 1988 in Saint-Petersburg, Russia



## About me

Senior iOS Software Engineer with more than 10 years of experience creating complex, user-focused software applications at the highest level of quality and efficiency. Started developing since iOS 3.0 in Objective-C and recently switched to Swift.

I am constantly learning new technologies and always try to improve my skills in this rapidly changing industry.

### Skills

Objective-C Swift

ReactiveCocoa | Rx

RxSwift

Texture (AsyncDisplayKit)

Core Data

Autolayout

VIPER

MVVM

REST | Git

Xcode

Carthage

Cocoapods

CI/CD

#### Contact

Saint-Petersburg

me@ayastrebov.com

+7 (931) 221 24 12

🔇 ayastrebov.com

AYastrebov



# Experience

### iOS Software Engineer

Mail.ru (Odnoklassniki) since May 2016

Member of Odnoklassniki iOS core team.

# Lead iOS Software Engineer

Luxoft

June 2015 - April 2016

Developing iOS apps for Tinkoff bank.

#### iOS Software Engineer

**Agile Fusion Corporation** 

July 2012 - June 2015

Developing iOS apps for U.S. customers.

## iOS and Android Software Engineer, Co-founder

FoodMap LLC

May 2011 - June 2012

iOS and Android app for spotting nearest cafes and restaurants and provides a full menu with a social integration.

# iOS Software Engineer

Lanit-Tercom

September 2010 - May 2011

Developing iOS apps.



#### Education

Specialist (Information technologies)

2006 - 2012

Saint-Petersburg State University, Mathematics and Mechanics Faculty.



#### Contributions

#### **RxSwift Community**

RxSwift ecosystem projects https://github.com/RxSwiftCommunity

#### CleanArchitectureRxSwift

Example of Clean Architecture of iOS app using RxSwift

https://github.com/sergdort/CleanArch itectureRxSwift